<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 1999-2021. Plesk International GmbH. All rights reserved. -->
<module>
  <id>domain-connect</id>
  <name>Domain Connect</name>
  <description>The Plesk Domain Connect Extension solves this issue by automatically configuring DNS for your website.</description>
  <category>dns</category>
  <url>https://plesk.com</url>
  <version>1.4.3</version>
  <release>{{RELEASE}}</release>
  <vendor>Plesk</vendor>
  <plesk_min_version>17.0</plesk_min_version>
  <!--Localized descriptions below-->
  <description xml:lang="ar">يعمل الملحق Plesk Domain Connect على حل هذه المشكلة من خلال تكوين DNS تلقائيًا لموقعك على الويب.</description>
  <description xml:lang="ca-ES">L'extensió Domain Connect de Plesk soluciona aquesta incidència, ja que configura el DNS pel seu lloc web de forma automàtica.</description>
  <description xml:lang="cs-CZ">Rozšíření Plesk Připojit doménu řeší tento problém automaticky konfigurací DNS pro váš web.</description>
  <description xml:lang="da-DK">Udvidelsen Plesk Domain Connect løser automatisk problemet ved at konfigurere DNS til dit websted.</description>
  <description xml:lang="de-DE">Mit der Erweiterung "Domain Connect" von Plesk können Sie dieses Problem beheben, indem Sie die DNS-Einstellungen für Ihre Website automatisch konfigurieren lassen.</description>
  <description xml:lang="el-GR">Η επέκταση Domain Connect του Plesk λύνει αυτό το πρόβλημα, διαμορφώνοντας αυτόματα τις ρυθμίσεις DNS για την τοποθεσία web σας.</description>
  <description xml:lang="es-ES">La extensión Domain Connect de Plesk soluciona esta incidencia configurando el DNS de forma automática para su sitio web.</description>
  <description xml:lang="fi-FI">Pleskin Domain Connect -laajennus ratkaisee tämän ongelman määrittämällä automaattisesti verkkosivustosi DNS-asetukset.</description>
  <description xml:lang="fr-FR">L'extension Plesk Domain Connect résout le problème en configurant automatiquement le DNS de votre site Web.</description>
  <description xml:lang="he-IL">ההרחבה Plesk Domain Connect פותרת בעיה זו על ידי קביעת תצורה אוטומטית של ה-DNS עבור אתר האינטרנט שלך.</description>
  <description xml:lang="hu-HU">Webhelye esetén, a DNS automatikus konfigurálásával, a Plesk Domainhez kapcsolódás bővítmény megoldja e problémát.</description>
  <description xml:lang="id-ID">Ekstensi Domain Connect Plesk memecahkan masalah ini dengan mengonfigurasi DNS secara otomatis untuk situs web Anda.</description>
  <description xml:lang="it-IT">L’estensione Domain Connect di Plesk risolve il problema configurando il DNS automaticamente per il tuo sito Web.</description>
  <description xml:lang="ja-JP">Plesk Domain Connect 拡張では、ウェブサイト用に DNS を自動構成することによってこの問題を解決します。</description>
  <description xml:lang="ko-KR">Plesk Domain Connect 확장 프로그램은 웹 사이트의 DNS를 자동으로 구성하여 이 문제를 해결합니다.</description>
  <description xml:lang="ms-MY">Sambungan Plesk Domain Connect menyelesaikan masalah ini dengan mengkonfigurasi DNS secara automatik untuk laman web anda.</description>
  <description xml:lang="nb-NO">Utvidelsen Plesk Domain Connect løser problemet ved å automatisk konfigurere DNS for nettstedet.</description>
  <description xml:lang="nl-NL">De extensie Plesk Domain Connect lost dit probleem op door DNS automatisch voor uw website in te stellen.</description>
  <description xml:lang="pl-PL">Rozszerzenie Plesk Domain Connect rozwiązuje ten problem, automatycznie konfigurując DNS dla Twojej witryny.</description>
  <description xml:lang="pt-BR">A extensão Domain Connect do Plesk resolve esse problema configurando automaticamente o DNS para o seu site.</description>
  <description xml:lang="pt-PT">A extensão Domain Connect do Plesk resolve este problema, configurando automaticamente o DNS para o seu site.</description>
  <description xml:lang="ro-RO">Extensia Plesk Domain Connect rezolvă această problemă prin configurarea automată a DNS pentru site.</description>
  <description xml:lang="ru-RU">Расширение Plesk Domain Connect решает эту проблему путем автоматической настройки DNS для вашего сайта.</description>
  <description xml:lang="sv-SE">Plesk Domain Connect-ändelse löser detta problem genom att automatiskt konfigurera DNS för din webbplats.</description>
  <description xml:lang="th-TH">ส่วนขยาย Domain Connect ของ Plesk ช่วยแก้ไขปัญหานี้โดยกำหนดค่า DNS ให้กับเว็บไซต์ของคุณโดยอัตโนมัติ</description>
  <description xml:lang="tl-PH">Nilulutas ng Plesk Domain Connect Extension ang isyu sa pamamagitan ng awtomatikong pag-configure sa DNS para sa iyong website.</description>
  <description xml:lang="tr-TR">Plesk Domain Connect Uzantısı, web siteniz için DNS'i otomatik olarak yapılandırarak bu sorunu çözer.</description>
  <description xml:lang="uk-UA">Розширення Domain Connect від Plesk вирішить цю проблему шляхом автоматичного налаштування DNS для вашого веб-сайту.</description>
  <description xml:lang="vi-VN">Tiện ích mở rộng Domain Connect của Plesk giải quyết vấn đề này bằng cách tự động định cấu hình DNS cho trang web của bạn.</description>
  <description xml:lang="zh-CN">Plesk 域名连接扩展可以自动为您的网站配置DNS，从而帮助解决这一问题。</description>
  <description xml:lang="zh-TW">Plesk 域名連接擴展可以自動為您的網站配置DNS，從而幫助解決這一問題。</description>
</module>
